<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VOLOC</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="nav_item_welcome">Welcome/Courses</string>
    <string name="nav_item_news_and_updates">News and Updates</string>
    <string name="nav_item_blog">Blog</string>
    <string name="nav_item_about">About US</string>

    <!-- navigation drawer item labels  -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>@string/nav_item_welcome</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_news_and_updates</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_blog</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_about</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_welcome">Welcome/Courses</string>
    <string name="title_news_and_updates">News and Updates</string>
    <string name="title_blog">Blog</string>
    <string name="title_about">About Us</string>
    <string name="question">\?</string>




    <!-- Documentation -->
        <string name="intro_documentation">The vedio is based on Android, at the end of
    vedio you should be able to learn to create simple and basic Android Application.</string>
    <string name="content_documentation">First open a blank Activity
    Then go to your content_main.xml file and with the help of drag and drop or code one text view, Edit text and a button.
    Now in the text view put the text "Welcome", set background as blue.
    Now Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH  Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH          Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH    Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH  Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
     Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH Blah blah BLAH
    And then on clicking the button the colour of the background should change to blue.</string>
    <string name="Testing_documentation">So to test it connect your devise or you can also use virtual machine.
    It is more preffered to use a devise reather than a virtual device to save your time.
    To test click on the green triangle pointing towards right side on your Android Studio.
    Once the apk is installed in your android device, the app would be launched automatically.
    Now click on the button, on clicking the button you would see that background color changes to blue from white.</string>
    <string name="summary_documentation">So at the end of this tutorial you should be able to make a simple Android Application.
    In this application you learned about how to change the color, simillary you can change thr text of the text_view with the help of intent.
    To learn how to create and launch new Activity see our next tutorial or follow our next documentation on "Launching new activity with Intent"</string>
    <!-- Documentation string ends -->
    <!-- Strings to change the mode -->
    <string name="menu_night_mode">Change the mode</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_system">Follow system</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_day">Day (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_night">Night (always)</string>
    <string name="menu_night_mode_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="Color">TextColor</string>


</resources>
